What you believe, what you know, is all how you spin it.
Spinning Man is a mystery, thriller, crime film directed by Simon Kaijser.
Evan Birch is a family man and esteemed professor at a distinguished university.
When a female student goes missing, police Detective Malloy has reason to be suspicious
when crucial evidence makes Evan the prime suspect in her disappearance.
Evan Birch, played by Guy Pearce.
Malloy, played by Pierce Brosnan.
Ellen Birch, played by Minnie Driver.
Anna, played by Alexandra Shipp.
Joyce Bonner, played by Odeya Rush.
Ross, played by Jamie Kennedy.
Spinning Man is a 2018 thriller film directed by Simon Kaijser based on a novel
by George Harrar and adapted to screenplay by Matthew Aldrich.
It stars Guy Pearce, Pierce Brosnan, Minnie Driver,
Alexandra Shipp, Clark Gregg and Odeya Rush.
The film was released on video on demand as well as experiencing
limited release by Lionsgate Premiere on April 6, 2018.
The film explores themes of lake, husband wife
relationship, cheerleader, suspicion, teenage girl.
The tone is intense and mind_bending.